Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Sharon Gordon papers, 1955-1979 RL.11161
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company. Sharon Gordon papers
1955-1979
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company
RL.11161
0.8 Linear Feet
Founded in 1864, the J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT) is one of the oldest and largest enduring advertising agencies in the United States. Sharon Gordon worked as an assistant to Colin Dawkins in the New York Office.
Arrangement
Arranged into two series: JWT News Files; and Offices.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The J. Walter Thompson Company. Sharon Gordon papers were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 1987.
Related Materials
Related materials may be found in the following J. Walter Thompson Company Archives collections held by the Hartman Center: Newsletters; Iconographic Collection; Colin Dawkins papers; International Offices
Collection Overview
Collection spans 1955-1979 and includes photographs, correspondence, biographical sketches, press releases, presentations and other printed materials Submitted to Ms. Gordon as part of her duties relative to assisting Colin Dawkins and the production of the JWT News publication. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Advertising agencies -- Employees; Advertising agencies -- United States; J. Walter Thompson Company
- JWT News Files, 1975-1979; 1
  - Book of Knowledge, 1978 (Box 1)
  - Desensitization of America, 1975-1978 (Box 1)
  - JWT London--Queen Elizabeth II Silver Jubilee, 1977 (Box 1)
  - Management changes, circa 1979 (Box 1)
  - Photographs, circa 1975-1979; 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Press releases, 1977 (Box 1)
  - Rena Bartos, 1976 (Box 1)
  - Retired JWT letters, 1975-1978 (Box 1)
- Offices, 1955-1979; 2
  - Amsterdam, 1975-1978 (Box 1)
  - Argentina, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Australia, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Austria, 1975-1977 (Box 1)
  - Brazil, 1975-1977 (Box 1)
  - Brussels, 1975-1977 (Box 1)
  - Caribbean, 1977-1978 (Box 1)
  - Germany, 1955-1977 (Box 2)
  - Greece, 1975-1977 (Box 2)
  - Indonesia, 1976 (Box 2)
  - Italy, 1975-1977 (Box 2)
  - Japan, 1975-1977 (Box 2)
  - London, 1976-1978 (Box 2)
  - Malaysia, 1976-1978 (Box 2)
  - Mexico, 1975-1977 (Box 2)
  - Peru, 1975-1977 (Box 2)
  - Philippines, 1977 (Box 2)
  - South Africa, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Spain, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Sweden, 1978 (Box 2)
  - Switzerland, 1975 (Box 2)
  - United States--Atlanta, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - United States--Chicago, 1975-1977 (Box 2)
  - United States--Detroit, 1977-1978 (Box 2)
  - United States--JWT West, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - United States--New York, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Uruguay, 1977 (Box 2)
  - Venezuela, 1975-1977 (Box 2)